A Guide to the Overseas Development Council records FA788
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Meetings, 1985-2000; 3; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
  - ODC Executive Committee Meeting, 1997 April 8 (Box 27, Folder 361)
  - Board Meeting - Notes, Comments, 1997 January (Box 27, Folder 362)
  - ODC Transition Executive Committee Meeting, 1996 December 6 (Box 27, Folder 363)
  - ODC Transition Executive Committee Meeting, 1996 April 12 (Box 28, Folder 364)
  - ODC Transition Executive Committee Meeting, 1996 February 16 (Box 28, Folder 365)
  - TEC Meeting, 1996 May 30 (Box 28, Folder 366)
  - TEC Conference Call, 1996 June 19 (Box 28, Folder 367)
  - TEC Meeting, 1996 July 26 (Box 28, Folder 368)
  - Nominees for Board and Council, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 369)
  - ODC Meeting, 1996 November 21-22; FA788:2016:016; 10 tapes (Box 28, Folder 369A)
    Researchers interested in accessing audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
  - Offitbank Report, 1996 December 6 (Box 28, Folder 370)
  - Transition - Concept Paper, 1994-1996 (Box 28, Folder 371)
  - Transition Executive Committee, 1995 October 11 (Box 28, Folder 372)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1995 June 9 (Box 28, Folder 373)
  - Transition Meeting, 1995 July 20 (Box 28, Folder 374)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1995 February 3 (Box 28, Folder 375)
  - ODC Board of Directors Meeting, 1995 October 11 (Box 29, Folder 376)
  - Meeting of the ODC Executive Committee, 1999 September 24 (Box 29, Folder 377)
  - ODC Finance Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 378)
  - Auditor's Report, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 379)
  - TEC Meeting Minutes, 1995 December 15 (Box 29, Folder 380)
  - Board of Directors - Resolutions Aprroved, 1993-1995 (Box 29, Folder 381)
  - Executive Committee Meeting - Executive Session, 1995 July 26 (Box 29, Folder 382)
  - ODC Board of Directors Meeting, 1995 February 21 (Box 29, Folder 383)
  - ODC Transition Executive Committee Meeting, 1995 December 15 (Box 29, Folder 384)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1994 October 11 (Box 29, Folder 385)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1994 September 23 (Box 29, Folder 386)
  - Meeting of the Nominating Committee, 1994 September 23 (Box 29, Folder 387)
  - Board of Directors Profile - Class of 1994, 1994 May (Box 29, Folder 388)
  - Offitbank Portfolio, 1994 September 23 (Box 29, Folder 389)
  - Board of Directors - Diversity Profile, 1994 September 1 (Box 29, Folder 390)
  - Council Diversity Profile, 1994 January 1 (Box 29, Folder 391)
  - ODC Board Meeting - JWS Presentation, 1994 October 11 (Box 30, Folder 392)
  - Annual Meeting of the Council, 1994 October 11 (Box 30, Folder 393)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1994 May 10 (Box 30, Folder 394)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1994 February 8 (Box 30, Folder 395)
  - ODC Nominating Comittee Mtg. - Cancelled, 1994 May 10 (Box 30, Folder 396)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1994 April 29 (Box 30, Folder 397)
  - Leadership Gifts Meeting, 1994 April 29 (Box 30, Folder 398)
  - ODC Members Joining Clinton Administration, 1993 August 9 (Box 30, Folder 399)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1993 September 10 (Box 30, Folder 400)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1993 December 17 (Box 30, Folder 401)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1993 October 13 (Box 30, Folder 402)
  - Annual Meeting of the Council, 1993 October 13 (Box 30, Folder 403)
  - Nominating Committee Meeting, 1993 July 8 (Box 30, Folder 404)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1993 May 13 (Box 30, Folder 405)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1993 April 30 (Box 30, Folder 406)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1993 February 11 (Box 30, Folder 407)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1993 April 30 (Box 31, Folder 408)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1993 February 11 (Box 31, Folder 409)
  - Reserve Fund History, 1993 May 10 (Box 31, Folder 410)
  - Investment Committee - Meeting Minutes, 1992 January 27 (Box 31, Folder 411)
  - Board of Directors Retreat, 1992 April 29-30 (Box 31, Folder 412)
  - Council Participation Profile, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 413)
  - Council Retirees, 1991 December 13 (Box 31, Folder 414)
  - Board of Directors Participation Profile, 1991 December 13 (Box 31, Folder 415)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1992 November 19 (Box 31, Folder 416)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1992 October 30 (Box 31, Folder 417)
  - Board of Directors Diversity Profile, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 418)
  - Board of Directors Attendance Policy, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 419)
  - Board of Directors - Committee Member Listing, 1993 March 12 (Box 31, Folder 420)
  - Board and Council Membership Profile, 1992 June (Box 31, Folder 421)
  - Participation Profile - Class of '91, 1991 December 13 (Box 31, Folder 422)
  - Annual Meeting, 1991 June 24 (Box 31, Folder 423)
  - Council Retirees, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 424)
  - Board of Directors Retreat, 1987 September 25-26 (Box 31, Folder 425)
  - Annual Meeting, 1988 December 7 (Box 31, Folder 426)
  - Annual Meeting, 1990 November 15 (Box 32, Folder 427)
  - Annual Meeting, 1985 November 13 (Box 32, Folder 428)
  - Meeting of the Executive Committee, 1985 October 23 (Box 32, Folder 429)
- Fundraising, 1994-2000; 4; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Miscellaneous Fundraising, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 430)
  - Diversifying ODC's Base, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 431)
  - USAID Cooperative Agreement, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 432)
  - USAID, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 433)
  - USAID, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 434)
  - USAID, 1996-2000 (Box 32, Folder 435)
  - African Aid Effectiveness, 1994-1998 (Box 32, Folder 436)
- Country Files, 1993-2000; 5; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - Canadian International Development Agency, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 437)
  - Canada, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 438)
  - Denmark, 1995-1998 (Box 32, Folder 439)
  - France, 1998-1999 (Box 33, Folder 440)
  - Japan, 1998-2000 (Box 33, Folder 441)
  - Japan International Cooperation Agency, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 442)
  - The Japan Foundation - Center for Global Partnership, 1994-1996 (Box 33, Folder 443)
  - Japan - CGP - Final Report, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 444)
  - Japan - CGP - Budget Narrative, 1993-1997 (Box 33, Folder 445)
  - Japan Foundation - Wakisaka's Publications, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 446)
  - Netherlands - Ministry of Foreign Affairs - The Hague, 1993-1996 (Box 33, Folder 447)
  - Spain, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 448)
  - Sweden, 1996-2000 (Box 34, Folder 449)
  - Swedish - SIDA, 1994-2000 (Box 34, Folder 450)
  - Swiss Development Cooperation Agency, 1995-2000 (Box 34, Folder 451)
  - Switzerland, 1998-2000 (Box 34, Folder 452)
  - United Kingdom, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 453)
  - United States, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 454)
- Kudos, Testimony, and Speeches, 6; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - Kudos, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 455)
  - Kudos, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 456)
  - Kudos, 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 457)
  - "ODC Was Right", 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 458)
  - Kudos, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 459)
  - Kudos, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 460)
  - Kudos, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 461)
  - Kudos, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 462)
  - Kudos, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 463)
  - Policy Focus Kudos, 1990-1993 (Box 34, Folder 464)
  - Kudos, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 465)
  - Kudos, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 466)
  - Kudos, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 467)
  - Kudos, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 468)
  - Bengt Save Soderbergh Breakfast - Cancelled, 1997 February 27 (Box 34, Folder 469)
  - Kudos, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 470)
  - Kudos, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 471)
  - Testimony, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 472)
  - Testimony, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 473)
  - Testimony, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 474)
  - Testimony, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 475)
  - Testimony, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 476)
  - Testimony, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 477)
  - Testimony, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 478)
  - Testimony, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 479)
  - Testimony, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 480)
  - Testimony, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 481)
  - Testimony, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 482)
  - Testimony, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 483)
  - Testimony, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 484)
  - Testimony, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 485)
  - Testimony, 1992-1995 (Box 36, Folder 486)
  - Testimony, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 487)
  - Speeches, 1976-1978 (Box 36, Folder 488)
  - Speeches, 1983-2000; Folder contains digital media (Box 36, Folder 489)
    Conditions Governing Access
  - "Privatization in the Third World" (JWS on American Interests), 2016:FA788:002; 1 VHS tape (Box 36)
  - Al-Hamad Dinner, 1996 April 23; FA788:2016:003; 2 cassette tapes (Box 36)
  - Cassettes, 1997 March 4; FA788:2016:004; 4 unique cassette tapes (Box 36)
  - Secretary General's Luncheon, 1999 May 4; FA788:2016:005; 2 tapes (Box 36)
  - ODC Conference on Employment, 1995 October 12; FA788:2016:006; 3 unique tapes (Box 36)
  - WOLA - ODC Peru Conference, 1985 April 9; FA788:2016:007; 3 tapes (Box 36)
  - ICRW Conference, 1995 July 21; FA788:2016:008; 3 tapes (Box 36)
  - Sutherland Dinner, 1997 January 23; FA788:2016:009; 1 tape (Box 36)
  - Fredericks Luncheon, 1996 December 9; FA788:2016:010; 1 tape (Box 36)
  - Maurice Strong Dinner, 1992 January 8; FA788:2016:011; 2 tapes (Box 36)
  - Cassettes, 1997 March 3; FA788:2016:012; 5 tapes (Box 36)
  - 4th Convocation, 1993 October 13-14; FA788:2016:013; 5 tapes (Box 36)
  - Investment and Competition Policy/Information Technology, FA788:2016:014; 6 tapes (Box 36)
  - EOSG Research Institute, 1999 May 4; FA788:2016:015; 8 tapes (Box 36)
- Press Clippings, 7; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
  - ODC in the News, 1985 December - 1986 November (Box 36, Folder 490, Folder 491, Box 37, Folder 492)
  - ODC in the News, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 493, Folder 494)
  - ODC in the News, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 495, Folder 496)
  - ODC in the News, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 497, Folder 498)
  - ODC in the News, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 499, Folder 500, Folder 501)
  - ODC in the News, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 502)
  - ODC in the News, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 503)
  - ODC in the News, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 504, Folder 505)
  - ODC in the News, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 506)
  - ODC in the News, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 507)
- Proposals and Projects, 1994-2000; 8; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - Aid Dependence - Managing a Transition - Sub S. Africa, 1998-2000 (Box 39, Folder 508)
  - Central Program Funding, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 509)
  - Congressional Staff Forum on International Development, 1997-1999 (Box 40, Folder 510)
  - Development and the Security of the Individual, 1997 April (Box 40, Folder 511)
  - Enhancing Security and Development, 1994 February (Box 40, Folder 512)
  - Environment, 1997 February (Box 40, Folder 513)
  - E-Commerce (Exxon), 2000 June (Box 40, Folder 514)
  - Governance in Africa, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 515)
  - IMF Working Group, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 516)
  - US International Engagement, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 517)
  - Multilateral Engagement, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 518)
  - Multilateral Research and Dialogue, 1997 January (Box 40, Folder 519)
  - Peacebuilding Program, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 520)
  - Pension and Health Care Reform - Eastern Europe and Latin America, 1997 May (Box 40, Folder 521)
  - Opportunities for Collaboration, 1999 April (Box 40, Folder 522)
  - Cornell Strategic Alliance, 1999-2000 (Box 40, Folder 523)
  - Meeting with Don Randel, 1999 October 15 (Box 40, Folder 524)
  - US Policy Program, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 525)
  - UN Think Tank Meeting, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 526)
  - Trade, Investment, and Development, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 527)
  - USAID Cooperative Agreement, 2000 January (Box 41, Folder 528)
  - US Policies on International Development Cooperation, 1997 March (Box 41, Folder 529)
  - World Health Cooperation Beyond 2000, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 530)
- Corporations, 1989-2000; 9; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
  - American Express Company, 1996-1998 (Box 41, Folder 531)
  - ARCO Chemical Company, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 532)
  - BPAmoco, 1998-2000 (Box 41, Folder 534)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1993-1997 (Box 41, Folder 535)
  - Corning Glass Company, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 536)
  - Dearfield Associates, Inc., 1989-1997 (Box 41, Folder 537)
  - Donaldson, Lufkin & Jenrette, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 538)
  - Duracell International, Inc., 1995-1997 (Box 41, Folder 539)
  - The Equitable Financial Companies, 1994-1995 (Box 41, Folder 540)
  - Exxon/ExxonMobil, 1994-2000 (Box 41, Folder 541)
  - FannieMae Foundation, 1996-1997 (Box 41, Folder 542)
  - Ford Motor Company, 1994-2000 (Box 42, Folder 543)
  - IBM Corporation, 1995-1998 (Box 42, Folder 544)
  - IFPMA, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 545)
  - International Paper Company, 1996-1998 (Box 42, Folder 546)
  - Merck & Company, Inc., 1988-1998 (Box 42, Folder 547)
  - J.P. Morgan - Morgan Guaranty Trust, 1994-1996 (Box 42, Folder 548)
  - Morgan Stanley Group, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 549)
  - New York Society for International Affairs, Inc., 1997 (Box 42, Folder 550)
  - Texaco Foundation, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 551)
  - Unilever United States, Inc., 1994-1998 (Box 42, Folder 552)
  - United Technologies Corp., 1994-1997 (Box 42, Folder 553)
  - The Washington Post Company, 1994-2000 (Box 42, Folder 554)
- Foundations, 1993-2000; 10; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
  - Atlantic Philanthropic Service Company, 1998-2000 (Box 42, Folder 555)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1994-2000 (Box 42, Folder 556)
  - Christian Children's Fund, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 557)
  - Ford Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 42, Folder 558)
  - Ford Foundation, 1996-1997 (Box 43, Folder 559)
  - Ford Foundation, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 560)
  - Ford Foundation, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 561)
  - Ford Foundation, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 562)
  - Philip L. Graham Fund, 1994-1998 (Box 43, Folder 563)
  - ICRW, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 564)
  - W. Kellogg Foundation, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 565)
  - Henry Luce Foundation, 1994-1998 (Box 43, Folder 566)
  - The John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1993-1997 (Box 43, Folder 567)
  - The John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1998-2000 (Box 44, Folder 568)
  - The Andrew Mellon Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 44, Folder 569)
  - The Joyce Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 44, Folder 570)
  - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1994-1996 (Box 44, Folder 571)
  - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 572)
  - Pew Charitable Trusts, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 573)
  - Pew Global Stewardship Initiative, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 574)
  - Ploughshares Fund, 1994-2000 (Box 44, Folder 575)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1994-2000 (Box 44, Folder 576)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1994-1999 (Box 44, Folder 577)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box 45, Folder 578)
  - Tinker Foundation, 1997-2000 (Box 45, Folder 579)
  - U.N. Foundation - Better World Fund, 1999-2000 (Box 45, Folder 580)
  - The Whitehead Foundation, 1998-2000 (Box 45, Folder 581)
  - The Winston Foundation for World Peace, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 582)
  - World Hunger Education Service, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 583)
- International Organizations, 11; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Asian Development Bank, 1991-1994 (Box 45, Folder 584)
  - Global Coalition for Africa, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 585)
  - Inter-American Development Bank, 1994-1998 (Box 45, Folder 586)
  - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 587)
  - United Nations Development Programme, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 588)
  - The World Bank, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 589)
- Publications, 12; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
  - Basic Needs, 1975-1993 (Box 45, Folder 590, Box 46, Folder 591)
  - Briefing Papers - The U.S. Economy and Developing Countries, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 592)
  - Defining the Development Agenda, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 593)
  - Japan Close-Up, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 594)
  - Challenges and Priorities in the 1990s, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 595)
  - A Globalization Summit, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 596)
  - Reducing Global Unemployment, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 597)
  - The Challenge of Mexico to U.S. Foreign Policy, 1997 June (Box 46, Folder 598)
  - U.S. and Asian Property Linked to Latin Debtor Growth, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 599)
  - Does Aid Have a Future?, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 600)
  - The 1994 Foreign Aid Budget, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 601)
  - Managing the International Economy in the Age of Globalisation, 1998 October 4 (Box 46, Folder 602)
  - What Future for Aid?, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 603)
  - The Partnership Imperative: Maintaining American Leadership in a New Era, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 604)
  - Rx for Global Health Cooperation Beyond 2000, 1998 April (Box 46, Folder 605)
  - Global Recovery: The Contribution of Developing Countries, 1983 May (Box 46, Folder 606)
  - Appropriate Indicators of Social Progress in the Sahel, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 607)
  - US-Japan Cooperation in a New Era, 1989-1991 (Box 46, Folder 608)
  - ODC Publications, 1994-1999 (Box 46, Folder 609)
  - Human Development: Research and Policy Choices, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 610)
  - The U.S.-Japan Economic Relationship in East and Southeast Asia, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 611)
  - The Metamorphosis of the Third World: U.S. Interests in the 1990s (Box 47, Folder 612)
  - U.S. Foreign Policy and Developing Countries: Discourse and Data 1991 (Box 47, Folder 613)
  - Perspectives on Aid and Development, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 614)
  - Making Peace Work: The Role of the International Development Community, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 615)
  - Intricate Links: Democratization and Market Reforms in Latin America and Eastern Europe, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 616)
  - Investing in Africa, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 617)
  - Poverty, Natural Resources, and Public Policy in Central America, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 618)
  - Como Hacer que la Apertura Funcione, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 619)
  - Managing a Smooth Transition from Aid Dependence in Africa, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 620)
  - Trade, Environment,and the WTO: The Post-Seattle Agenda, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 621)
  - Reforming Health and Education: The World Bank, The IDB, and Complex Institutional Change, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 622)
  - Emerging Agenda for Global Trade: High Stakes for Developing Countries, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 623)
  - Moving to the Market: The World Bank in Transition, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 624)
  - Miracle or Design? Lessons from the East Asian Experience, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 625)
  - Pressing for Peace: Can Aid Induce Reform?, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 626)
  - North-South Environmental Strategies, Costs, and Bargains, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 627)
  - Encouraging Democracy: What Role for Conditioned Aid?, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 628)
  - Debt Conversion in Latin America: Panacea or Pandemic?, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 629)
  - After the Wars, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 630)
- Financial Records, 13; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
  - Forms 1099 and 1096, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 631, Folder 632)
  - Forms 1099 and 1096, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 633)
  - Forms 1099 and 1096, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 634)
  - Forms 1099 and 1096, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 635)
  - Forms 1099 and 1096, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 636)
  - Forms 1099 and 1096, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 637)
  - Forms 1099 and 1096, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 638)
  - Forms 1099 and 1096, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 639)
  - Forms 1099 and 1096, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 640)
  - Forms 1099 and 1096, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 641)
  - Forms 1099 and 1096, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 642)
  - Forms 1099 and 1096, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 643)
  - Forms 5500, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 644)
  - Forms 5500, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 645)
  - Forms 5500, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 646)
  - Forms 5500, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 647)
  - Forms 5500, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 648)
  - Form 5500, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 649)
  - Form 5500, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 650)
  - Form 5500 C/R, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 651)
  - Form 5500, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 652)
  - Form 5500, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 653)
  - Form 5500-C, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 654)
  - Form 5500-C, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 655)
  - Form 5500-C, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 656)
  - Form 5500-R, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 657)
  - Form 5500-R, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 658)
  - Form 5500-C, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 659)
  - Form 5500-C, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 660)
  - Form 5500-C, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 661)
  - Form 5500-C, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 662)
  - Form 5500-C, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 663)
  - Form 990, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 664)
  - Form 990, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 665)
  - Form 990, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 666)
  - Form 990, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 667)
  - Form 990, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 668)
  - Form 990, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 669)
  - Form 990, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 670)
  - Form 990, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 671)
  - Form 990, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 672)
  - Form 990, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 673)
  - Form 990, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 674)
  - Form 990, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 675)
  - Form 990, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 676)
  - Form 990, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 677)
  - Form 990, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 678)
  - Form 990, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 679)
  - Form 990, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 680)
  - Form 990, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 681)
  - Form 990, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 682)
  - Form 990, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 683)
  - Form 990, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 684)
  - A-133 Filing Information, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 685)
  - New York State, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 686)
  - New York State, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 687)
  - New York State, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 688)
  - New York State, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 689)
  - New York State, 1974-1992 (Box 53, Folder 690)
  - New Jersey Registration, 1982 November (Box 53, Folder 691)
  - Audit Work Papers: Long-Term Assets, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 692)
  - Audit Work Papers: Assets, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 693, Folder 694)
  - Audit Work Papers: Liabilities and Net Assets, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 695, Folder 696)
  - Financial Records, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 697-700)
  - Audit Papers, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 701, Box 56, Folder 702-704)
- Overseas Development Council Photographs, 1972-2000; 14; 4.52 Cubic Feet 11 letter document boxes, 1 half-letter document box and 1 photo box
  Photographs
  - Board Dinner, 2000 March 7 (Box 57, Folder 705-706)
  - Board Meeting/Dinner, 1998 October 13-14 (Box 57, Folder 707)
  - Rodrik Book Release - Pangestu Breakfast Briefing, 1999 January (Box 57, Folder 708)
  - Mr. Sutherland and ODC President, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 709)
  - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 710)
  - World Bank Conference, 1986 June (Box 57, Folder 711)
  - Omni Shoreham Conference, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 712)
  - Omni Shoreham Conference, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 713)
  - Staff Photos (Box 57, Folder 714)
  - ODC Meeting at U.N., 1999 May 4-5 (Box 58, Folder 715)
  - IMF Meeting, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 716)
  - Peter Sutherland Headshots (Box 58, Folder 717)
  - Globalization Conference, 1999 March 18 (Box 58, Folder 718-722)
  - J. Brian Atwood Farewell Speech, 1999 June 29 (Box 59, Folder 723)
  - Asia Conference, 1998 March 19 (Box 59, Folder 724)
  - Congressional Staff Forum, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 725)
  - World Bank Conference, 1986 June (Box 59, Folder 726-727)
  - ODC Staff, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 728-729)
  - Susan Rice CSF, 1998 April 22 (Box 60, Folder 730)
  - Trade and Investment Conference, 1998 January 22 (Box 60, Folder 731)
  - Perspectives on Aid and Debt Conference, 1997 December 16 (Box 60, Folder 732)
  - Af. Fin. Ministers, 1997 April 29 (Box 60, Folder 733)
  - Sutherland Dinner, 1997 January 23 (Box 60, Folder 734)
  - Iglesias Lunch, 1996 January 25 (Box 60, Folder 735)
  - Board Meeting, 1997 October 15 (Box 60, Folder 736)
  - Africa Conference, 1996 June 11-12 (Box 60, Folder 737)
  - Wayne Fredericks Lunch, 1996 December 9 (Box 60, Folder 738)
  - Princeton, 1994 June (Box 60, Folder 739, Box 61, Folder 740-741)
  - Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 61, Folder 742)
  - World Summit Copenhagen, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 743)